
    Oversee implementation of quality assurance strategies, methodologies and metrics collection, with a heavy emphasis on quality upstream.
    Drive and refine software quality assurance best practices to enhance testing capabilities within embedded QA teams.
    Identify process gaps, champion and lead initiatives to strengthen overall product quality.
    Manage internal quality assurance teams responsible for Quality Assurance, Performance, Tools and Automation.
    Provide weekly dashboard report to the Head of QA.
    Collaborate with QA Leads and review test plans to ensure technical accuracy, compliance, completeness, and to mitigate risks.
    Review bugs found by quality assurance teams and work with Dev/QA Leads to determine priorities for fixes.
    Proactively engage with planning, design and development teams to promote prevention of defects early in project/development life cycles.
    Recruit, manage, mentor, and develop a talented high performing team of in house technical Quality Engineers.
    Implement application performance assurance through techniques such as: performance profiling, performance testing, and load testing standards.
    Work closely with Product Development, Release and Product teams to prioritize assignments and manage risks/issues to ensure successful delivery.
    Provide leadership and technical guidance to the QA team, while instilling creativity, accountability, and teamwork.
    Perform other duties as they arise.
